<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intune on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://deploymentshare.com/tags/intune/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intune on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/tags/intune/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 8 - Autopilot Devices</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-8-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-8-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll look at pulling in details about Autopilot devices. Our list call from Managed Devices, covered in part 6 , gives us a column to tell us whether that device is autopilot enrolled but what if we want more information than that? What if we want to know the group tag it uses or whether it has an autopilot profile assigned to it. Lets go get that!&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 7 - Managed Applications</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-7-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-7-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll look at Applications within Intune. The Graph response for this will have some additions for applications at the bottom for cross referencing purposes so check those out too. Especially if you use PatchMyPC.&#xA;Lets get to it!&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon! - Connectors and Tokens Table Of Contents Graph URL Global Pre-requisites Chose your method Create the query Explanation Relationships Supported Product Lists Additional Next post Graph URL The graph URL we are using in this section is deviceAppManagement/mobileApps/.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 6 - Managed Devices</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-6-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-6-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In this post we are finally going to look at getting some data into PowerBI to play around with. We are going to use a query in PowerBI to go and retrieve our managed devices information. Remember discussing pagination for APIs? Should you have more than 1000 devices we&amp;rsquo;re also going to need to consider Pagination but don&amp;rsquo;t worry there are three methods to do this discussed below.&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 5 - Heavy Lifting</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-5-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-5-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at using Logic Apps and OData.Feed to do the &amp;lsquo;heavy lifting&amp;rsquo; for us. By heavy lifting, essentially this is handling pagination of the Microsoft Graph Call. Using the app registration permissions for authorisation to the data, then processing the result in order to make sure we have all the data we need and finally passing the results back to PowerBI so that its handled outside of PowerBI. PowerBI only cares about the data.&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 4 - Get-BearerToken</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-4-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-4-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In the previous posts, we talked about obtaining an access token (bearer token) to access the data in our environments. We even looked at using our first POST query to post a request for a token in PostMan. The reason I&amp;rsquo;ve called this post &amp;lsquo;Get-BearerToken&amp;rsquo; is because I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain how to use a combination of PowerBI Variables and a function to leverage the Application Registration we have to get a bearer token within PowerBI Desktop. We can then use that bearer token to authenticate against the Microsoft Graph and start to pull data into PowerBI like we did in the PostMan application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-3-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-3-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>Next up, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the Graph and the URLs and permissions, in this post, continuing on from Part 1 and Part 2 , our next step is begin to firstly understand our path to getting Intune Data into PowerBI, which is going to be via direct Microsoft Graph calls - Remembering of course that the Intune Data warehouse did not meet our requirements. We are also going to leverage an application registration to access the data we want to see. This is gonna be a BIG post, so make sure you have plenty of time to read.&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 2 - Application Registration</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-2-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-2-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>Continuing from Part 1 , our next step is to establish an application registration in Azure. This registration will enable us to utilise its permissions for accessing data on the Microsoft Graph and hopefully then, importing that data into PowerBI. This setup is essential as it serves as a global prerequisite for accomplishing our ultimate objective.&#xA;Quick Links Series Menu Part 1 - Where to Start Part 2 - Application Registration Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs Part 4 - Get-BearerToken Part 5 - Heavy Lifting Part 6 - Managed Devices Part 7 - Managed Applications Part 8 - Autopilot Devices Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 1 - Where to Start</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-1-pbi-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-1-pbi-intune/</guid>
      <description>In this series, I will guide you through the process of extracting data from Microsoft Graph, specifically Microsoft Intune, and integrating it into PowerBI. We will explore different approaches, considering their advantages and disadvantages, in order to provide you with a solid foundation for creating your own reports within your specific environment. Its intent is to take you on a journey as I discover what to do, so please do take the time to read them in order to ensure you come along for the ride! I have invested significant time and effort into studying this subject and understanding the potential pitfalls associated with various approaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting a Group Tag During a Configuration Manager Task Sequence</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-apgrouptagts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-apgrouptagts/</guid>
      <description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about using the Windows autopilot deployment for existing devices Task sequence in configuration manager and modifying that task sequence to set a group tag during the process. You may know that traditionally this tasks sequence is used to &amp;lsquo;build&amp;rsquo; devices and have them ready to start the autopilot process. I had a customer recently that had that very need. They had purchased a large number of machines that were delivered with Windows 10 installed and not Windows 11. As the customer was on their Windows 11 uplift journey already they were a bit disappointed to say the least and they opted to create a Configuration Manager task sequence to prep them for autopilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logon to Autopilot HAADJ Devices Using FortiClient VPN</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-forticlient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-forticlient/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a customer who uses FortiClient as their VPN solution, and they have recently embarked on setting up Hybrid AAD. We set their tenant up, sorted out licensing and I started to put in the fundamental elements to begin the journey to using Autopilot for provisioning devices. I had undertaken setting up AAD connect and using IDFix to remediate any issues, such as UPN suffixes for end-users via PowerShell, and we were ready to go. Equally, I had made them an Intune Win32app for FortiClient, and this installed and removed just fine using PSADT. I had already tested the Autopilot process and things were looking good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit and Intune Win32 Apps</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadtintune/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadtintune/</guid>
      <description>Hi Folks! Leading on from this post about getting started with PSADT, and as promised, I’m writing up my experience with it and creating Win32 Intune apps. So firstly, I’m assuming by now that you read and absorbed the first write up I did, you should have noticed that a couple of things I did in that post can actually be done differently and be eager and armed with understanding the format and have a good idea about what to do. Combine that with great ‘google-fu’ and you’re ready to continue your decent app packaging journey. Using this with ConfigMgr applications is quite simple because once you’ve prepared your application you use the root folder as the source content for the application and the rest is pretty straight forward (holler at me if you want that blogging too).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit Write Up</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, thought I’d write up what I’ve been working on recently, which is re-visiting PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit. A great Resource for ConfigMgr apps, but equally it is supported in Intune so I will be doing a follow-up post on using this with Intune. I know there are plenty of blogs out there on this so this is just my interpretation and is intended to get people started. I know, for example, that the kit comes with a wide variety cmdlets that you can utilise to achieve tasks but this write up is based around getting those a little familiar with PowerShell up to speed with it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
