<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PowerBI on Deploymentshare | Personal Tech Blog</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/tags/powerbi/</link><description>Recent content in PowerBI on Deploymentshare | Personal Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:30:45 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/tags/powerbi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>INTUNE AND POWERBI DEEP DIVE - PART 6 - GET-DEVICES</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-6-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:30:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-6-pbi-intune/</guid><description>In this post we are finally going to get some data into PowerBI to play around with. We are going to look at forming a query in PowerBI, then to use it to go and retrieve our devices and their information. Remember discussing pagination for APIs? Well&amp;hellip; should you have more than 1000 devices we&amp;rsquo;re also going to need to consider Pagination.
Now, you might consider employing a coding mindset akin to PowerShell, such as fetching the initial 1000 devices and implementing a do-while loop to retrieve the remaining ones using a method such as checking for the presence of another @Data.</description></item><item><title>INTUNE AND POWERBI DEEP DIVE - PART 5 - LOGIC APP</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-5-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-5-pbi-intune/</guid><description>In this post we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at using logic apps to do the &amp;lsquo;heavy lifting&amp;rsquo; for us. By heavy lifting, I mean taking our bearer token for authentication to the tenant, using the app registration permissions for authorisation to the data, then processing the result from the Microsoft Graph API call (pagination) in order to make sure we have all the data we need then finally passing the results back to PowerBI, so we can make a nice dashboard out of the results.
Logic App Design / Build So, lets take a look at the Logic App used in the calls we might make in the upcoming sections</description></item><item><title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 4 - Get-BearerToken</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-4-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 21:54:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-4-pbi-intune/</guid><description>The reason I&amp;rsquo;ve called this post &amp;lsquo;Get-BearerToken&amp;rsquo; is because I&amp;rsquo;m going to explain how to use a combination of PowerBI Variables and a function to leverage the Application Registration we have to get a bearer token within PowerBI Desktop. We can then use that bearer token to authenticate against the Microsoft Graph and start to pull data into PowerBI. If you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, a Graph response will provide a maximum of 1000 replies and the rest of the replies will be split into chunks, known as pages. So page 1 contains responses 1-1000, page 2 1001-2000 and so on and so forth.</description></item><item><title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 3 - Exploring Graph URLs</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-3-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:10:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-3-pbi-intune/</guid><description>Next up, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the Graph and the URLs and permissions, in this post, continuing on from Part 1 and Part 2 , our next step is begin to firstly understand our path to getting Intune Data into PowerBi, which is going to be via direct Microsoft Graph calls - Remembering of course that the Intune Data warehouse did not meet our requirements. We are also going to leverage an application registration to access the data we want to see. This is gonna be a BIG post, so make sure you have plenty of time to read.
Quick Links We&amp;rsquo;re going to explore the Microsoft Graph URLs, the structure of them, how to obtain what we need and some tools to test them to ensure we&amp;rsquo;ve got them correct.</description></item><item><title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 2 - Application Registration</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-2-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:41:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-2-pbi-intune/</guid><description>Continuing from Part 1 , our next step is to establish an application registration in Azure. This registration will enable us to utilize its capabilities for accessing data on the Microsoft Graph and seamlessly importing that data into PowerBI. This setup is essential as it serves as a prerequisite for accomplishing our ultimate objective.
Quick Links Creating the App Reg This is going to be a &amp;lsquo;whistle stop tour&amp;rsquo; of setting up an application registration. Consider this a condensed guide that will provide you with the necessary steps. As you progress and develop your PowerBI data sets, you can always revisit specific parts of this process to add additional permissions, granting you access to more data.</description></item><item><title>Intune and PowerBI Deep Dive - Part 1 - Where to Start</title><link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-1-pbi-intune/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:10:45 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-1-pbi-intune/</guid><description>In this series, I will guide you through the process of extracting data from Microsoft Graph, specifically Microsoft Intune, and integrating it into PowerBI. We will explore different approaches, considering their advantages and disadvantages, in order to provide you with a solid foundation for creating your own reports within your specific environment. Its intent is to take you on a journey as I discover what to do, so please do take the time to read them in order to ensure you come along for the ride! I have invested significant time and effort into studying this subject and understanding the potential pitfalls associated with various approaches.</description></item></channel></rss>