<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://deploymentshare.com/categories/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting SAML Auth on FortiClient VPN when applying NCSC Baselines</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-forticlient-ts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-forticlient-ts/</guid>
      <description>Dearest gentle reader&amp;hellip; (Yes, my wife is making me watch that Bridgerton series on netflix, so I may speak like a 19th century gentlemen during this blog post&amp;hellip; or not&amp;hellip;) I recently blogged about the implementation of Center for Information Security (CIS) and how those configurations broke Windows Autopilot. It then developed into a series on CIS with another gentleman of the manor, Nick Benton. And so, speaking of security posture, I recently undertook a customer engagement where they wanted to modernise their Windows Management and explore Entra joined only devices using Autopilot, but also, to align all their security configuration to National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) - which of course I did but in doing so this broke their SAML authentication on Forticlient VPN - so here&amp;rsquo;s the story of how I fixed it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intune Defender for Endpoint Connector</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-dfec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-dfec/</guid>
      <description>Defender for Endpoint, are you licensed for it? Are you using it? Are you using Intune? Then why are you not using the Intune Connector for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE)? In this article I will hope to explore this on your behalf and share my findings. Microsoft Defender for Endpoint and Intune can be integrated to enhance your organisation&amp;rsquo;s security posture by enabling endpoint protection, threat detection, and response capabilities across all managed devices. This integration allows for the sharing of security information and the application of compliance policies based on threat intelligence.&#xA;So, what do we need to be able to use this?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIS Intune Baselines - What do they break?</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-cis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-cis/</guid>
      <description>(And yes I know&amp;hellip;. AI Generated blog post images are beginning to get a bit cringe&amp;hellip; but I actually liked this one so I rolled with it)&#xA;Hello again folks, today we&amp;rsquo;re talking CIS. What is it and more specifically what does it break? Here in the UK, everyone talks about NCSC baselines and adhering to Cyber Essentials or Cyber Essentials Plus and for both of these there is some guidance you can follow with suggestions that help you improve your security posture. NCSC even provide some (old) JSON files for Windows Configuration for configuration profiles you can download and import to Intune to get you started.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
