<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration Manager on Deploymentshare | Personal Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://deploymentshare.com/categories/configuration-manager/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration Manager on Deploymentshare | Personal Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/categories/configuration-manager/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting a Group Tag During a Configuration Manager Task Sequence</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-apgrouptagts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-apgrouptagts/</guid>
      <description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about using the Windows autopilot deployment for existing devices Task sequence in configuration manager and modifying that task sequence to set a group tag during the process. You may know that traditionally this tasks sequence is used to &amp;lsquo;build&amp;rsquo; devices and have them ready to start the autopilot process. I had a customer recently that had that very need. They had purchased a large number of machines that were delivered with Windows 10 installed and not Windows 11. As the customer was on their Windows 11 uplift journey already they were a bit disappointed to say the least and they opted to create a Configuration Manager task sequence to prep them for autopilot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build apps in Endpoint Manager</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-applications/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, I hope you are all safe and well.&#xA;I’ve been thinking about writing this for a while and I hope it helps some of you new to app packaging.&#xA;How do I build apps? It never hurts to brush up if you’re a seasoned app-packager. App packaging isn’t going away any time soon, everyone needs apps. The Microsoft app store has gotten better but I don’t feel it’s quite there yet in terms of broadly available applications. Sometimes, companies can have line-of-business applications that they build in-house and as system administrators, you may be responsible for packaging and distributing those applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit Write Up</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-psadt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/post/bp-psadt/</guid>
      <description>Hi all, thought I’d write up what I’ve been working on recently, which is re-visiting PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit. A great Resource for ConfigMgr apps, but equally it is supported in Intune so I will be doing a follow-up post on using this with Intune. I know there are plenty of blogs out there on this so this is just my interpretation and is intended to get people started. I know, for example, that the kit comes with a wide variety cmdlets that you can utilise to achieve tasks but this write up is based around getting those a little familiar with PowerShell up to speed with it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
