<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration Manager on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://deploymentshare.com/categories/configuration-manager/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration Manager on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/categories/configuration-manager/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Handy Windows 11 Collections for Configuration Manager</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-w11-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-w11-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready for Windows 11?  No?  Why not?  Windows 10 deadline is fast approaching - just look at the title image its already starting to fade away&amp;hellip; I kid you not October will be here quick as a flash and there&amp;rsquo;s much to do.  Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve had a couple of Configuration Manager customers, starting their journey to Windows 11 and as a result I thought I&amp;rsquo;d create this short blog post on some useful Configuration Manager collections I&amp;rsquo;ve used to aid my customers on their journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A well-structured deployment strategy is crucial for a smooth rollout, and some customers still use Microsoft Configuration Manager (SCCM/MEMCM) which plays a strong role in certain upgrade plans. As with dynamic membership rules in Intune, one of the most powerful tools within Configuration Manager is its ability to create dynamic device collections from a massive plethora of conditions, allowing IT teams to segment and control deployments with more precision.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting a Group Tag During a Configuration Manager Task Sequence</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-apgrouptagts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-apgrouptagts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/autopilot/tutorial/existing-devices/deploy-autopilot-task-sequence&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Windows autopilot deployment for existing devices Task sequence&lt;/a&gt; in configuration manager and modifying that task sequence to set a &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/autopilot/enrollment-autopilot&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;group tag&lt;/a&gt; during the process.  You may know that traditionally this tasks sequence is used to &amp;lsquo;build&amp;rsquo; devices and have them ready to start the autopilot process.  I had a customer recently that had that very need.  They had purchased a large number of machines that were delivered with Windows 10 installed and not Windows 11.  As the customer was on their Windows 11 uplift journey already they were a bit disappointed to say the least and they opted to create a Configuration Manager task sequence to prep them for autopilot.  That prep process was to include wiping the device and re-loading with Windows 11, adding the device to the tenants autopilot devices AND setting a group tag to drop the device into pre-created groups that control the apps and configurations the devices are going to receive during autopilot.&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build apps in Endpoint Manager</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-applications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, I hope you are all safe and well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about writing this for a while and I hope it helps some of you new to app packaging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ins&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-build-apps&#34;&gt;How do I build apps?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ins&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It never hurts to brush up if you’re a seasoned app-packager. App packaging isn’t going away any time soon, everyone needs apps. The Microsoft app store has gotten better but I don’t feel it’s quite there yet in terms of broadly available applications. Sometimes, companies can have line-of-business applications that they build in-house and as system administrators, you may be responsible for packaging and distributing those applications. How do you tackle it? where do you begin?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit Write Up</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all, thought I’d write up what I’ve been working on recently, which is re-visiting PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit.  A great Resource for ConfigMgr apps, but equally it is supported in Intune so I will be doing a follow-up post on using this with Intune.  I know there are plenty of blogs out there on this so this is just my interpretation and is intended to get people started.&#xA;I know, for example, that the kit comes with a wide variety cmdlets that you can utilise to achieve tasks but this write up is based around getting those a little familiar with PowerShell up to speed with it.  There are many ways to skin a cat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
