<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PowerShell on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://deploymentshare.com/tags/powershell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PowerShell on Deploymentshare - Personal Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://deploymentshare.com/tags/powershell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit and Intune Win32 Apps</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadtintune/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadtintune/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Folks!&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;Leading on from &lt;a href=&#34;articles/bp-psadt/&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; about getting started with PSADT, and as promised, I’m writing up my experience with it and creating Win32 Intune apps.&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;So firstly, I’m assuming by now that you read and absorbed the first write up I did, you should have noticed that a couple of things I did in that post can actually be done differently and be eager and armed with understanding the format and have a good idea about what to do.  Combine that with great ‘google-fu’ and you’re ready to continue your decent app packaging journey.&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;Using this with ConfigMgr applications is quite simple because once you’ve prepared your application you use the root folder as the source content for the application and the rest is pretty straight forward (holler at me if you want that blogging too).  Putting that into Intune however is slightly different.  There are many blog posts about Intune Content Prep Tool however in a nut-shell, this tool will take your content (source) files for your application, and output a single .intunewin file which is the file format that Intune understands.&#xA;So lets go ahead and download the tool from here and extract it to a local folder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit Write Up</title>
      <link>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://deploymentshare.com/articles/bp-psadt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi all, thought I’d write up what I’ve been working on recently, which is re-visiting PowerShell App Deployment Toolkit.  A great Resource for ConfigMgr apps, but equally it is supported in Intune so I will be doing a follow-up post on using this with Intune.  I know there are plenty of blogs out there on this so this is just my interpretation and is intended to get people started.&#xA;I know, for example, that the kit comes with a wide variety cmdlets that you can utilise to achieve tasks but this write up is based around getting those a little familiar with PowerShell up to speed with it.  There are many ways to skin a cat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
